

# Marco Abel Zefanya

Jakarta Selatan | 081294150023 | marcoabel25@gmail.com

### **About Me**

I'm Marco Abel Zefanya graduated from Gunadarma University with a bachelor's degree in engineering, worked as a Quality Assurance Engineer, to ensuring high quality standard code for automatic cars transmission systems for 2 years. I have a good communication skill, able to work in team and under pressure, have great problem solving, attention to detail. I am very interested in Software Quality Assurance field, and Web Development field, especially back-end.

### **Personal Skill**

- HTML / CSS / Bootstrap
- PHP
- MySQL JavaScript
- Golang
- C
- Version Control System (Git)
- Teamwork
- Leadership Skill
- Time Management
- Adaptive
- Problem Solving

## **Work Experience**

### PT SYS Indonesia

Software Quality Assurance (Sept 2021 - Nov 2023)

White Box testing for automotive transmissions, which requires a deep proficiency in the C programming language, using winAMS tools, and excel formulas.

# Quality Assurance of BMW and FIAT Project

We are as a team doing white box testing for automatic transmission for BWM, and FIAT car. We must reach 100% precentage from Coverage Testing, find and fixing the bugs, and make reporting file to QA Lead.

## Quality Assurance of A Spice/Volkswagen Project

- Analyze data and review the requirements needed to test a product
- Make plans for detailed tests, test cases based on the source code
- Conduct testing with the unit testing method
- Finding and fixing bugs in the source code Preparing test result report to the QA Lead

### PART TIME – PT KAI Data Entry PT KAI Expo (2017 - 2018)

Collecting data from all customers, grouping by their destination,

and double checking to customers about their ticket before inserting the data into database.

**Organization & Volunteer Expriences** 

## Main Gate Ticketing Supervisor

**TPS Crew** 

ASIAN PARA GAMES 2018

Monitoring and handling the crowded at Main Gate Ticketing Supervisor in

**Gelora Bung Karno** Gate 5 ASIAN GAMES JAKARTA PALEMBANG 2018

# Main Gate Ticketing Supervisor

Monitoring and handling the crowded at Main Gate Ticketing Supervisor in

**Gelora Bung Karno** Gate 5 RELAWAN TPS PEMILIHAN GUBERNUR DAN WAKIL GUBERNUR DKI JAKARTA 2017

Monitoring and counting the result from the vote, Cilandak Barat region

# Ticketing Crew (2017 and 2018)

PART TIME - Asian Sound Syndicate

Scanning and Validating ticket before enter the venue

 PART TIME - Shawn Mendes The Tour 2019 Ticketing Crew (8 October)

# Scanning and Validating ticket before enter the venue

PART TIME - Divide World Tour 2019 Jakarta

Ticketing Crew (5 May 2019)

Scanning and Validating ticket before enter the venue

**Education History** 

Bachelor of Informatic Engineering - GPA 3.21/4.00

2013 - 2016

2016 - 2020

 Senior High School **SMA Bakti Idhata** 

Gunadarma University

- **Tools Skill**

Visual Studio Code, Notepad ++

- Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint
- Figma winAMS

Postman

- Katalon Studio
- XAMPP

Find me on:

netlify

**Linked** in